Ending
Good Morning
Good morning.
Let's go.
Come on, what day is it today?
Today is the day before
Oh, it's the morning before.
It's the day before rehearsal.
Yes, sir.
Okay, off to school.
This is Yuri.
Good luck.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
I'll be with you all day.
Oh, no.
I'm busy.
I'm so busy, it's really hard to do that.
I'm too busy for that.
Go, go, go, go, go
We're all in this together
Go, go, go. We're not making much progress.
It might be the last time Asuka wears earphones.
Last time?
Earmuffs.
It might be the last time.
I'm going to put this transmitter in my pants.
Uh, yes.
Thank you for the launch information.
My name is Aska.
I think it's the second one I've had.
I think it's pretty busted.
Which one is the right one? Red is right?
Red is right.
I forgot.
I can hit it all the way out, and I don't think I care which one it is now.
When you're at the exchange, you're behind the paper hand.
Behind the paper hand, you can see the customers a little bit.
If you don't get out, you can't see the customers behind the lower hand.
I think it's better to hit that area.
Thank you for your time, staff.
I'll be the last one for the next three days.
I'm sure everyone thinks this is a live performance by Nogi Pig.
I'd be happy if you could make everyone look pretty and light up.
I would be very happy if you could light up the stage.
I look forward to working with you for the next three days.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
# Lay down the letter, touch it, invisible to the eye, formless, in the heart, I can get it
(Lay down the letter and touch it) (Lay down the letter and touch it) (Lay down the letter and touch it) (Lay down the letter and touch it) (Lay down the letter and touch it)
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
Tell me if you can't.
Four-hour changeover, alarming.
The best you can do, ViThe ste für duty.
53h ability 40h security
The best
Heart, you are the best
Thank you for watching
I think it would be better for our guests
Please wait
Yes, it's all right.
You're hiding it in the mountains, right?
Yes, I'm hiding it.
Shall we go back one last time, then?
Okay. Okay.
What are you going to do now?
We're going to ride the bird puppet.
Bird puppet.
Thank you for watching.
If we go over, we'll bring it up. Slowly. Pace yourself.
If it's on the screen, it's on the screen.
You're filming.
End of rehearsal
Before drum rehearsal
I'm dancing all the time, aren't I?
More than I expected.
Did you dance the balloon?
Balloons are fun!
Bird and Fish Balloon Fun
That was so much fun.
I turned into a bird and fish.
I wish I could wear a bird and fish cap.
It would be so cute to wear it and ride on it!
I won't do it, won't do it, won't do it, won't do it, won't do it!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Jarter! Jarter!
Yum!
Still, I'm sure we'll all be sober before school.
I can't do anything.
Lack of energy.
Yum!
Cute.
He's so cute.
This one is happy.
It is a blue bird that calls for seafood, so it is blowing a lot of clovers.
Music
You look kind of bad.
Yup.Yeah. - Yeah.
Bye.
Thank you very much.
See you tomorrow.
Bye, bye, bye.
It's lunchtime.
Isn't it just past midnight?
You know, I like it this way.
I like to eat lunch at a proper lunch time.
Can you introduce today's menu?
I'm having mille-feuille today.
Eggplant.
Boiled vegetables.
Add some meat.
Put some meat in it.
Put the meat in the meat in the meat in the meat
Put the meat in the meat
Champur-like
There was also a cafe in there
They had strawberry milk, which I haven't always seen
They have strawberry milk, right?
You think I'm stupid, don't you?
I'm sure you're making fun of it.
But it looks kind of real tasty. I'll have some later.
No?
What? What do you mean?
I can have a drink any time I want.
I'm always ready to drink.
Here.
Are you sure?
I feel different.
Remember.
This guy.
I can't hear you.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm really okay.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Ophsy.
As much as I try my best during this period.
Actually...
I have a jet story to tell.
We will have a goal excitement!
Thanks everyone!
Thank you for watching!
What's with the strawberry milk?
I'll take strawberry milk with me.
Isn't that strawberry?
Do you want ice? Here.
Why don't you take it home?
Is it cold?
It'll be too thin.
It's getting thin?
Even the staff.
All the way down here.
I'll take it home with me.
It's the second day.
Laughs.
You don't have to run away so hard.
Laughing.
Yes, Asuka's meal today is...
Fantastic!
If you spill it on this
Tri-colored bread
Yeah, that's why it tastes like...
I wonder what it tastes like
Oh, this...
Chocolate.
Good morning.
Thank you for watching.
Nice deck.
There?
Thank you for watching.
Remember...
Oh...
Oh, no...
I'm sorry it's just you guys.
I hope this is more of the same.
Hey.
Wow!
Cute.
Oh, I don't like it.
I didn't forget this.
I'm a little uncertain,
I don't think it's as scary as you think.
What?
The one you wrote for the first lesson.
Oh, yeah.
Did you accomplish this?
Yes!
I never thought about the libretto.
Grow up.
Please take it home.
Embarrassing.
Thank you very much.
Nice.Great.
I welcomed a few times as hard as I could.
April 21, 2014 Deeply Zo got the shaved ice.
Let's see what happens.
Voila.
It became your mother's hot wire.
Chan chan chan
Yuki Village
Chang, chang, chang, chang.
Bon appétit!
Thank you for watching.
Now then, thanks to all of you, I was able to graduate in a very flowery way,
I have a lot to be thankful for,
I would like to wish for the happiness, health and development of all of you here and all those who are involved with you,
This time, I would like to say yo!
Yo!
Kankon!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
We have a lot of guests.
We have a lot of customers
Full of customers
Let's go inside the store
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for your time
Did you take my picture?
Oh, I see.
LOL.
Let's see...
Thank you very much.
Thank you for following us so closely.
I'm so glad we were able to finish the graduation school successfully.
It was a lot of fun!
I'll make sure to put the logo on it.
It's been a long time since I've been able to speak out.
It's been a while since I've seen the members
It's been a long time since I've seen the members perform.
It was so much fun to see them live
It was so much fun!
I'll be back.
I'll see you all soon.
I'm sure you'll all continue to watch
I'm sure you will continue to watch
Nobisaka46Please support Nobisaka46
Please support us!
See you soon!
Good Channel
Channel Good Button
Good Button and
Channel Button
Channel Registration
Good Button and Channel Subscribe
Thank you!
Bye, bye, bye!
[ED
The End